Min Aung Thu Win

Mid-senior Web Developer

© Mawlamyine, Mon State, Myanmar

Profile

I am a creative, hardworking, and open-minded web developer with a passion for building robust web applications that meet the needs of clients. With more than two years of professional experience in web development, I have a solid understanding of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and DOM API, and I have extended my knowledge by using modern web frameworks such as React.js, Vue.js, SvelteKit and so on. Additionally, I possess a strong understanding of backend technologies like Linux servers, document databases, and more. I believe in writing clean, maintainable, and concise code as an essential part of software engineering.

As a mid-level web developer, I am dedicated to continuous learning and professional development to stay on top of the latest trends and best practices in web development. I am enthusiastic about applying my skills and knowledge to new challenges and opportunities in the field.

Personal Info

Email

mhemaungthuwin@gmail.com

Phone

+95 978 366 8091

Linkedin

www.linkedin.com/in/aung-thu-win/

GitHub

github.com/Oungseik

Languages

English - Intermediate

Mon - Native tongue

Burmese - Native tongue

Archivements

• Best of award for 2022 first half - by Qualy Myanmar Inc

Work History

April 2023 - Present

Full-stack Developer at Kiosk

- Create 3D object render web-application with Vue.js.
- Create back-end server with **Nodejs,DynamoDB** for database and store user uploaded files in the **AWS S3 bucket**.
- Deploy on AWS EC2 instance with Ubuntu OS and use NginX as the reverse proxy.

March 2022 - April 2023

Web Developer at Qualy Myanmar Inc

- Create websites which meet the requirement of client while following the guidelines of **W3C** and **Web AIM**.
- Structure the WordPress Dashboard for the client to use as easy

as possible.

Create email service and deploy with Nodejs.

2019 - 2022

Vounteer Developer at GreenTech Inc

- Research and help each others in school projects.
- Share knowledge between passionate students and on Facebook.

Education

January 2014 - November 2018	Studied Bachelor of Mathematics from Mawlamyine University.
2003 - March 2013	Studied Basic Education from Thukhawaddy, Basic Education High School.

Skills and Experiences

- Successfully created and deploy a Web application in AWS EC2 instance under two months which can upload files for each user, view 3D object by using Vue.js in the front-end, Express.js in the backend, stored data in the DynamoDB and stored files on the AWS S3.
- Have strong knowledge of Back-end development with Express.js, modern Asynchornous
 Programming with Javascript and Nodejs. Able to write type-safe code in JavaScript with the help of JsDoc syntax and TypeScript. I created with Express js and Socket.io https://chat-app-zli5.onrender.com/ which support realtime chatting, realtime active status and session-based login.
- Have knowledge of front-end frameworks such as React, Vue and Svelte, and modern rendering patterns such as Client-side Rendering, Server-side Rendering, Hydration, Partial-hydrations Island Architecture and so on. Able to create fast, responsive and semantic website with Tailwindcss and WebAIM guidelines.
- Used Ubuntu linux since 2019. Have strong knowledge with linux command line programs such as BASH, VIM, TMUX and managing resources with CLI. Able to work with Linux environment without GUI.
- Proficient in Javascript and have the knowledge of various programming languages such as TypeScript, Rust, Haskell, Python and PHP. Able to write clean, concise, maintainable code by following functional programming languages patterns such as higher-order function, currying, partial-application, Monoid and clean code principles.